<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Module 1: Pre-Build QA on AWS DevSecOps Modernization Workshop</title>
    <link>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Module 1: Pre-Build QA on AWS DevSecOps Modernization Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction</title>
      <link>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/1_introduction.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/1_introduction.html</guid>
      <description>Objective: To assure quality of the code committed before the build creation In software development, build refers to the process of converting files and other assets under developer&amp;rsquo;s responsibility into a software product in its final (or) consumable form. These activities cover: Compile source files -&amp;gt; Package compiled files into compressed formats (like jar, zip) -&amp;gt; Produce installer’s -&amp;gt; Create (or) update Database schema (or) data
In DevOps, tests are designed and automated even before the code is written.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Build &amp; Execute</title>
      <link>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/2_build_execute.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/2_build_execute.html</guid>
      <description>PIPELINE CREATION AND EXECUTION To deploy the pipeline, run the following commands in Cloud9’s terminal:
aws cloudformation create-stack --stack-name PreBuildQA --template-url https://aws-wrkshp-artifacts.s3-eu-west-1.amazonaws.com/awsworkshop_infrastructure_artefacts/awsworkshop_prebuild_qa.json --capabilities CAPABILITY_NAMED_IAM Go to the CloudFormation console and check the status of your pipeline stack creation, named &amp;lsquo;PreBuildQA&amp;rsquo;. It should state - “CREATE_IN_PROGRESS”.
This step takes approximately ~1minute and if successful, you can see the status of STACK - ‘PreBuildQA’ as “CREATE_COMPLETE”, as shown in the screenshot below:  Please click on your stack name.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Debug &amp; Fix</title>
      <link>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/3_debug_fix.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/3_debug_fix.html</guid>
      <description>DEBUGGING AND RE-EXECUTION To debug the issue, from the AWSCodeBuild you can go to CodeBuild section &amp;ndash;&amp;gt; Report History and click on the latest failed link under Test Reports History.
You can then view the below report. Click on the failed test case to see the reason for failure.
Alternatively, please switch to your Reporting Dashboard and go to the section UnitTest to view the summary of this stage. Click on the component to view detailed test report to spot where the test failed.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Report &amp; Analysis</title>
      <link>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/4_test_reports_analysis.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/4_test_reports_analysis.html</guid>
      <description>TEST REPORTS ANALYSIS To view the CodeQuality and test coverage reports, use SONARQube dashboard for code quality metrics.
Refer the screenshot as shown below for more details:
To view the details of unit test, use the reporting dashboard for all statistics.
Refer the screenshot as shown below for more details:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tikk Talk</title>
      <link>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/5_tikk_talk.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/5_tikk_talk.html</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary</title>
      <link>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/10_summary.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-hugo.web.app/30_pre_build_quality_assurance/10_summary.html</guid>
      <description>The cost of fixing an error grows exponentially as it proceeds undetected through the SDLC. Pre-build QA helps in detecting issues early on and preventing the costs of software errors. Especially from a DevOps perspective, it paves way for early testing, bringing in the required agility in the QA cycles and speeding up the time to market.
Well done! You have successfully fixed the error and executed Pre-Build Quality Assurance Pipeline.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>