<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Prerequisites on AWS DevSecOps Modernization Workshop</title>
    <link>https://aws-hugo.web.app/10_prerequisites.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Prerequisites on AWS DevSecOps Modernization Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://aws-hugo.web.app/10_prerequisites/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Create an AWS account</title>
      <link>https://aws-hugo.web.app/10_prerequisites/1_aws_account.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-hugo.web.app/10_prerequisites/1_aws_account.html</guid>
      <description>Your account must have the ability to create new IAM roles and scope other IAM permissions.
 If you already have an AWS account, and have IAM Administrator access, you can skip this page.
   If you do not already have an AWS account with Administrator access: create one now
  Once you have an AWS account, ensure you are following the remaining workshop steps as an IAM user with administrator access to the AWS account: Create a new IAM user to use for the workshop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Register with Cognizant</title>
      <link>https://aws-hugo.web.app/10_prerequisites/2_create_a_cognizant_account_to_access_workshop_content.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://aws-hugo.web.app/10_prerequisites/2_create_a_cognizant_account_to_access_workshop_content.html</guid>
      <description>In addition to the workshop itself, we are pleased to offer you several thought leadership and research pieces about testing from a few experienced testing experts at Cognizant. We ask that you kindly register yourself at: https://www.cognizant.com/application-modernization
 Steps for Registration  Click on the Link Provide following input in the given form:   First and Last Name Update Company Update Email ID Update Industry Update Job Title  Click on Register Button  Estimated time required to complete registration: 2 minutes.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>